:00000018:

[00000001]
Stocke awakes injured in an
Alistel hospital. The distortion
in history begins here...{end}

[00000002]
Who were the odd people that
Stocke met on the way to
Granorg?{end}

[00000003]
Stocke's party sneaks into the
castle to assassinate Eruca,
queen of Granorg.{end}

[00000004]
Stocke manages to escape with
the Resistance's help, but
more hardship awaits...{end}

[00000005]
Stocke leaves Alistel to Rosch
and must fight Granorg.
However...{end}

[00000006]
With Garland's assistance, the
battle against Granorg's
General Dias is about to begin.{end}

[00000007]
Stocke embarks on a journey to
find comrades to help him free
Granorg.{end}

[00000008]
Heiss fails to assassinate
Eruca, but something strange
is happening to her...{end}

[00000009]
Rosch's small unit has new
orders to carry out.
What awaits them...?{end}

[0000000A]
Stocke goes to Gran Plain to
meet Rosch, while secret plans
are being carried out.{end}

[0000000B]
Alistel's evil arms have begun
to reach towards the peaceful
Celestia, forest of mana...{end}

[0000000C]
War had begun between Alisten
and Celestia. What news has
come to the battlefield...?{end}

[0000000D]
Will the proposed treaty with
the Gutrals be approved? It
seems this war will never end.{end}

[0000000E]
The battle with Alistel
intensifies. What desperate
acts did General Hugo take?{end}

[0000000F]
The messenger of death visits
the now-peaceful Granorg.
Stocke is called to the ruins.{end}

[00000010]
???{end}

[00000011]
???{end}

[00000012]
???{end}

[00000013]
???{end}

[00000014]
???{end}

[00000015]
???{end}

[00000016]
???{end}

[00000017]
???{end}

[00000063]
???{end}
