:00000218:

[00000001]
美切雲危救ダミテキスト{end}

[0000000A]
Stocke was given orders by
Heiss to meet an informant at
Lazvil Hills. Stocke is given
the White Chronicle.{end}

[0000000B]

Marco and Raynie joined Stocke.
However, he had a vision of
them dying.{end}

[0000000C]
Rosch shows up to see Stocke
off. He's Stocke's comrade and
best friend.{end}

[0000000D]

Rosche can't shake the inexplicable
feeling that something bad will
happen to Stocke.{end}

[00000014]
Stocke and the party headed to
rendezvous with the informant.
{end}

[00000015]
Upon making contact, however,
their source was assassinated.{end}

[00000016]
Stocke was ambushed by Palomides
the Executioner. The vision had come
true. Seriously wounded, Stocke
jumps into a river.{end}

[00000017]

Stocke arrived in a place
called Historia. Here he
meets two twins.{end}

[00000018]
Stocke traveled back in time
to avoid Palomides and breaks
through the blockade.
{end}

[00000019]
His party returns to Alistel
with their informant.{end}

[0000001E]
Stocke awakens in Alistel Castle's
infirmary. He and Sonja are attacked.
{end}

[0000001F]
Rosch saves Stocke and Sonja
from the attack, but the invader
turns to sand after his defeat.{end}

[00000020]
Nobody knows if the Sand Plague is
connected to the desertification
of the continent.
{end}

[00000021]

Even so, Stocke is ordered to
keep the details of his attack
under wraps.{end}

[00000032]
Rosch asked Stocke to join his
Brigade. Now he must decide to
join Rosch, or stay in Specint.{end}

[00000033]

Stocke realizes that this is a
critical decision.{end}

[00000046]
Stocke decides to stay in Specint.
Heiss now orders Stocke to acquire
intel from the Item Shop so Stocke
can capture Vlad.{end}

[00000047]

Stocke learns that Vlad will
appear in the bar.{end}

[00000048]
Stocke successfully subdued and
arrested Vlad outside the bar.
Now he must report back to Heiss.{end}

[00000050]
Stocke accepts Rosch's invitation.
His first mission under Rosch
is to clear the Granorg forces
out of Alma Mine.{end}

[00000051]

Stocke heads to the Mine via
Lazvil Hills.{end}

[0000005A]
Heiss tells Stocke that his next
mission will send him into Granorg.
He will be behind enemy lines.
{end}

[0000005B]
Stocke must meet an informant
under a bridge at Lazvil Hills
for new intel.{end}

[00000064]
Upon arriving at Alma Mine,
Stocke finds that it is caved in.{end}

[00000065]
Should he destroy the rocks to
storm the mine or ambush the
enemy here? He faces a critical
choice.{end}

[0000006E]
Stocke decided to ambush the
enemy, but it was a big loss of
time.{end}

[0000006F]
While his party stayed with the
mission, a detached force stormed
the capital. Alistel is lost.{end}

[00000082]
Stocke needs explosives to remove
the rocks, but the explosives
merchant is nowhere to be seen.{end}

[00000083]
Your actions in the alternate
timeline have changed this timeline.
The merchant arrived this time.{end}

[00000096]
With the rocks cleared from the
mine's entrance, the battle against
Granorg will finally begin.{end}

[00000097]

Stocke and his comrades eliminated
the Granorg forces, and returned
home victorious.{end}

[000000A0]
Marco and Raynie will accompany
Stocke on his mission to Granorg,
but Stocke needs to meet them in
town, first.{end}

[000000AA]
While Stocke and the party rested,
they met Kiel, who had been sent
by Sonja.
{end}

[000000AB]
Stocke heads for the castle's
infirmary.{end}

[000000B4]
After meeting up with Marco and
Raynie, Stocke now heads to meet
Heiss' agent.
{end}

[000000B5]
The agent should be waiting to
meet Stocke under the bridge.{end}

[000000BE]
Stocke didn't wait for the agent
and made his move, winning the
battle at Alma Mine.
{end}

[000000BF]
However, the Alistellian army
crumbled under contant pressure
from Granorg.{end}

[000000C8]
The agent never showed up.
Stocke wonders if he should go
on to the mine or continue waiting.{end}

[000000D2]
Stocke waited, but to no avail.
What happened to the agent?
{end}

[000000D3]
Stocke's actions in the other timeline
altered this timeline, and the agent
arrives. He tells Stocke to go through
the Sand Fortress.{end}

[000000DC]
While heading to the Sand Fortress,
Stocke and his party hear a cry
for help.{end}

[000000E6]
The explosives merchant was
being attacked by a group of
bandits who called themselves
the Desert Crows.{end}

[000000F0]
The Sand Fortress is under Granorg
control. In order to reach Granorg,
Stocke must break through their
defensive line.{end}

[000000F1]

Stocke's party defeats all the
enemies barring their path.{end}

[000000FA]
Stocke saves a Beastkind girl
whose friends offer to get Stocke
through the Granorg checkpoint.{end}

[00000104]
Stocke chose to force his way
through the checkpoint, causing
Granorg to tighten security.
{end}

[00000105]
This made Stocke's trip into
Granorg take even longer. The
informant was long gone. Stocke
failed in his mission.{end}

[0000010E]
The guards were unwilling to let
Stocke pass.{end}

[0000010F]

He must decide whether to force
his way through, or find another
method.{end}

[00000118]
After Stocke claimed to be an
entertainer, the guard demanded
to see a performance.
{end}

[00000119]
Stocke performed the sword dance
he had learned from Kiel, and was
allowed through. The group heads
to a campsite in the west.{end}

[00000122]
Aht taught Stocke how to use
"Mana Sight" so that he could
find firewood more easily.{end}

[0000012C]
Stocke was asked to gather five
pieces of firewood for the camp.{end}

[0000012D]

As Stocke gathers firewood, Aht calls
him over to the south hill.{end}

[0000012E]
Aht and Stocke team up to kill a
huge boar, and bring their firewood
back to the campsite.{end}

[0000012F]

After resting for a night, the group
now heads for Granorg.{end}

[00000136]
The group comes across a deceased
traveler. Aht sends the soul of the
traveler to heaven. She told Stocke
this was her true job.{end}

[00000137]

Stocke learned that Aht was a
shaman.{end}

[00000140]
Stocke has finally reached Granorg,
where the Alistellian agent is
waiting for him.
{end}

[00000141]
After thanking the entertainers,
Stocke now heads to the business
district.{end}

[0000014A]
Stocke's next mission is to
assassinate Princess Eruca. She's
rumored to be connected to the
Resistance.{end}

[0000014B]

Stocke must now find a way into
the Palace.{end}

[00000154]
The Rosch Brigade had won its
first victory. Stocke and Rosch
head to Lt. General Raul's office
for their next mission.{end}

[00000155]

Raul orders the Brigade to head
for Judgement Cliff for full
mission details.{end}

[0000015E]
The Brigade heads through Lazvil
Hills on their way to get further
orders at Judgement Cliff.{end}

[00000168]
The Brigade was told to report to
Field Marshal Viola at the Sand
Fortress.
{end}

[00000169]
But something about the informant
roused Stocke's suspicion. Stocke
chases after him.{end}

[0000016A]
Stocke captured the informant
and tried to interrogate him.
However, the informant suddenly
turned to sand.{end}

[00000172]
Stocke warns Rosch, but doesn't
mention the Sand Plague. They
continue on towards the Sand
Fortress.{end}

[00000173]

Rosch's Brigade arrives at the
Sand Fortress and must report
to Field Marshal Viola.{end}

[0000017C]
Stocke is given leave to explore the
fortress while Rosch reports in.{end}

[00000186]
Kiel teaches Stocke the art of
Sword Dancing as thanks for
Stocke teaching him swordsmanship.{end}

[00000190]
Reports that state that Field
Marshal Viola's troops are facing
long odds are relayed to the Sand
Fortress.{end}

[00000191]

Rosch must decide to either
dispatch rescue forces or defend
from within the fortress.{end}

[0000019A]
Rosch dispatched forces to aid
Viola, but the enemy anticipated
this.
{end}

[0000019B]
Dias sent more troops to exploit
the divided defenses. They were too
much to overcome.{end}

[000001A4]
Dias' knights were a feint, so
Stocke allowed them to breach
the Sand Fortress.
{end}

[000001A5]
Stocke disarms their bombs using
Mana Sight. This shifts the battle
in the defenders' favor.{end}

[000001AE]
Stocke and the others are ordered
to hold the fortress while Viola
is engaged in battle.{end}

[000001AF]

They succesfully hold and defend
the Sand Fortress from the
Granorgite invaders.{end}

[000001B8]
The Rosch Brigade will be honored
in a ceremony for their defense
of the Sand Fortress.
{end}

[000001B9]
Rosch and Kiel return to Alistel
to attend the ceremony.{end}

[000001D6]
The stage has been set for Alistel's
full invasion of Granorg.
{end}

[000001D7]
Rosch was assigned the task of
scouting the enemy forces. Stocke
is tasked with covering Rosch's
exfiltration.{end}

[000001E0]
Heiss traveled back in time to
assassinate Eruca before Stocke
could meet her.
{end}

[000001E1]
Stocke pursued Heiss and
stopped him from killing
Eruca, Stocke's sister.{end}

[000001EA]
Stocke has discovered that
underground waterways in Granorg
may be a way into the palace.{end}

[000001EB]
Stocke decided to investigate the
area behind a local tavern after
talking to a nervous barkeep.{end}

[000001F4]
The party encounters Claire in the
underground waterway and decides to
help her return to the surface.{end}

[000001F5]

Claire thanked the party for
aiding her out of the waterway.{end}

[000001FE]
The underground waterways are
a maze of twisted passages, mostly
alike. Stocke has to use switches
in order to go where he wishes.{end}

[00000208]
Stocke played decoy, and the
assassination seemed successful.
However, Marco and Raynie were
captured.{end}

[00000209]

Later, discrepancies about the
killing arose... The truth surrounding
this event may never be known.{end}

[00000212]
The passage connecting the castle
to the underground waterway
is tightly guarded. Stocke can't
just plow through.{end}

[00000213]

Stocke must find some way to mask
his presence.{end}

[0000021C]
Palace security is ironclad. Stocke
has to use some kind of special
skill to get through.{end}

[00000226]
Stocke used the Vanish skill he
learned while battling Heiss to
bypass security. He searches for
Princess Eruca.{end}

[00000227]

He found a figure on the balcony
that looked like the Princess.{end}

[00000228]
The figure turned out to be
a trap, and the group is
forced to flee the palace.{end}

[00000230]
Resistance forces aid Stocke's
party's escape. Stocke learns
that Eruca leads the Resistance.{end}

[00000231]

Stocke is told that Queen Protea
must be dethroned to perform a
ritual to stop the desertification.{end}

[00000232]
Eruca asks Stocke to join her
quest to save the world.{end}

[0000024E]
Stocke returned to the past with
documents that detailed an ambush
on the Rosch Brigade.
{end}

[0000024F]
Upon seeing the plans, Field Marshal
Viola dispatches Thaumatech
soldiers to Gran Plain.{end}

[00000258]
The invasion of Gran Plain has begun.
Stocke heads west to rendezvous
with the Rosch Brigade.{end}

[00000262]
Stocke reached the rendezvous
point, but the Rosch Brigade
was already facing annihilation.{end}

[0000026C]
Thanks to Stocke's quick thinking,
the Alistel forces emerged victorious.{end}

[0000026D]

But the price of victory was high...
Stocke lost his best friend, Rosch,
in the battle.{end}

[00000276]
The Rosch Brigade is in grave
danger. Stocke and his party
must move quickly to save them.{end}

[00000280]
Stocke retrieved some documents
from a dead Granorg soldier. It
appears that the Rosch Brigade
walked right into a trap.{end}

[0000028A]
Viola increased the pace of the
campaign, so Stocke rejoined
Rosch earlier than expected.{end}

[0000028B]

However, Rosch was still gravely
wounded. Kiel sacrificed himself
as a decoy to save Rosch.{end}

[00000294]
Stocke took Rosch back to Alistel,
but Rosch's wounds are severe.
An emergency operation is
necessary.{end}

[00000295]

During this, Raul asks Stocke to
search Hugo's office for evidence
of a setup.{end}

[0000029E]
When Stocke snuck into Hugo's
office, he found Heiss waiting
for him.{end}

[0000029F]
After a battle with Heiss, Stocke
mastered the Vanish skill.{end}

[000002A8]
Stocke obtained proof of Hugo's
betrayal, but this made him a
target. He must now flee Alistel.{end}

[000002B2]
Stocke leaves Alistel, taking Rosch
and Sonja with him. He is forced
to confront the pursuers so Rosch
and Sonja can flee.{end}

[000002B3]

All the pursuers are slain, but Stocke
succumbs to his injuries as well.{end}

[000002BC]
Having been saved by the Resistance,
Stocke and his party must put a
halt to their mission. They leave
Granorg and head to Cornet Village.{end}

[000002C6]
When Stocke regains consciousness,
he finds himself in Celestia.{end}

[000002D0]
A soldier in the Resistance, Will, has
asked Stocke to bring him a Sand
Sword.
{end}

[000002D1]
Stocke gave Will the Sand Sword he
had asked for.{end}

[000002DA]
Ricky guides Stocke to Cornet
Village.
{end}

[000002DB]
Ricky suggests that Stocke visit
the village mayor.{end}

[000002DC]
Stocke and Marco gave serious
thought to what Eruca had told
them, but Raynie does not feel
comfortable helping Eruca.{end}

[000002E4]
A brutal operation to crush the
Resistance in Granorg has begun.
Stocke returns to save Eruca.
{end}

[000002E5]
Despite her hesitation, Raynie
decides to aid Stocke.{end}

[000002F8]
When Stocke returns to Granorg,
he finds the city engulfed in flames.{end}

[00000302]
Will managed to survive the carnage
thanks to the Sand Sword Stocke
had given him.{end}

[0000030C]
Stocke learned that Eruca was in a
nearby bar.{end}

[0000030D]

Will fled the town after leaving
Eruca in Stocke's care.{end}

[00000316]
Aht was also entangled in the battle
at Granorg. After Stocke saves her,
she volunteers to accompany him.{end}

[0000032A]
Stocke makes contact with Eruca,
but Pierre sealed the escape route.
He had defected.{end}

[00000334]
Pierre realizes his mistake with
Claire's help. Thanks to Claire,
everyone manages to escape.{end}

[0000033E]
Eruca was rescued from Granorg.
{end}

[0000033F]
Now the party heads to the Sand
Fortress to rendezvous with Otto.{end}

[00000340]
Eruca forgave Pierre, and he
fled to Cornet Village with
Claire.{end}

[00000352]
Stocke reached the Sand Fortress,
but Otto was badly wounded.{end}

[0000035C]
Palomides' squad was approaching
from the rear, but Will appeared
during this dire moment and helped
Otto.{end}

[00000366]
Otto stalls Palomides' squad to
ensure Eruca's safety.
{end}

[00000367]
Stocke also manages to escape
with the help of Will and Otto.{end}

[00000370]
The party arrives at Judgement
Cliff. They head for a cave to make
camp.{end}

[0000037A]
After leaving watch duty to Marco,
Stocke is awoken by a scream.
{end}

[0000037B]
Rosch and Eruca had killed each
other...{end}

[00000384]
The party arrived at the campsite
with Aht's help. Marco volunteers
for the first watch shift.{end}

[0000038E]
In order to save Eruca, Stocke
is forced to kill Rosch. There may
be a way to prevent this fight
from happening.{end}

[0000038F]

Stocke managed to change Rosch's
mind in a different timeline,
avoiding the fatal clash.{end}

[00000398]
Rosch resides in Celestia after he
left Alistel. He tells Stocke to help
Eruca.{end}

[00000399]
 '         {end}

[000003A2]
Rosch's physical wounds have
healed, but losing his Gauntlet and his
men has sapped him of his
will to fight.{end}

[000003AC]
Celestia's leader, Barranca, asks
Stocke to help by defeating the
monsters near the village.{end}

[000003AD]

Stocke rescued Vanoss and his
troupe from monsters. {end}

[000003B6]
Vanoss reported that it is only
a matter of time before Alistel
defeats Granorg.
{end}

[000003B7]
Both Stocke and Vanoss feel that it
would be wise to go to Alistel to view
the current situation.{end}

[000003B8]
Stocke asked Vanoss to allow him to
accompany Vanoss on the trip.{end}

[000003C0]
After arriving in Alistel, Stocke hears
that Hugo will address the nation
soon.
{end}

[000003C1]
Hugo announced plans to wage war
on Cygnus and even the Beastkind.{end}

[000003CA]
Stocke was summoned by a
mysterious figure. He finds Raul
at the meeting.{end}

[000003D4]
While taking Raul to Celestia,
Stocke saves Elm by defeating
the Alistellian soldiers at the
forest entrance.{end}

[000003DE]
In order to repair Rosch's
Gauntlet, Stocke must find new
Core Parts.
{end}

[000003DF]
The parts to repair the Gauntlet
are in Alistel. What if Sonja
was asked in the past?{end}

[000003E0]
Stocke gave the core parts to
Sonja. She can now repair the
Gauntlet.{end}

[000003E8]
Raul talked to Barranca upon
arriving in Celestia.
{end}

[000003E9]
Celestia decides to join the war,
but they need a commander for
their forces.{end}

[000003F2]
Raul decided to lead the army. He
leads them to numerous victories.
{end}

[000003F3]
But in the end, he is felled by an
Alistellian assassin.{end}

[000003FC]
Rosch is most suitable to lead the
army, but he's still mentally unable
to fight.
{end}

[000003FD]
Once Sonja has the Force Core,
Stocke challenges Rosch to a fight,
hoping to awaken his fighting spirit.{end}

[00000406]
After fighting Stocke, Rosch's
spirit is reignited.
{end}

[00000407]
The battle between Celestia and
Alistel draws near...
{end}

[00000438]
The Force Core was removed
from the broken Gauntlet.{end}

[00000442]
After coming to, Stocke finds
himself in prison, and is forced
to fight as a gladiator.
{end}

[00000443]
Stocke continued to fight in order
to find the rest of his comrades.{end}

[0000044C]
Stocke is now a gladiator in Cygnus.
{end}

[0000044D]
Garland realizes Stocke's might and
challenges him.
{end}

[0000044E]
Stocke defeats Garland and is
welcomed as a guest.
{end}

[00000456]
Aht was sold to a tavern in Cygnus.
Stocke frees her.{end}

[00000460]
Stocke begins searching for Eruca
and the others.
{end}

[00000461]
An information broker promises to
tell Stocke the location of the
woman brought to the city with him
if he defeats his brother in combat.{end}

[0000046A]
Stocke is victorious in his first
tournament battle.
{end}

[0000046B]
His second opponent, Bram, the
Desert Crow, also falls to Stocke.{end}

[00000474]
In order for Stocke to win, Aht
spends all her life force to release
the power of Chi.
{end}

[00000475]
However, Aht's death is too high a
cost to pay for this victory.{end}

[0000047E]
Stocke now faces the information
broker's brother.
{end}

[0000047F]
The information broker's brother
is a skilled fighter who uses the
power of Chi.{end}

[00000488]
Stocke must find a way to defeat
the power of Chi. He was told of a
Gutral who defeated the gladiator
in the past.{end}

[00000489]

If Stocke can use the skill he
learned from Gafka, he may stand
a chance.{end}

[00000492]
Stocke was victorious against
the Chi user, but there are
still other foes left.{end}

[0000049C]
Stocke finally defeats the Chi user.
Now he is able to get information
from the broker.{end}

[0000049D]

His female friend is being held in an
underground prison.{end}

[0000049E]
The information broker set up a
plan for Stocke to disguise himself
as someone delivering food.{end}

[000004A6]
Stocke's next opponent is a huge
beast.
{end}

[000004A7]
After the beast is defeated, the
annoucer states that Stocke will
face an even stronger foe.{end}

[000004B0]
While attempting to rescue Eruca,
Marco and Raynie reunite with Stocke.
{end}

[000004B1]
A giant spider breaks up the
reunion, and Stocke decides to
fight it to protect the city.{end}

[000004BA]
The Hell Spider was slain. Stocke's
party defended the city.
{end}

[000004BB]
However, how will Garland react to
Stocke freeing Eruca from prison?{end}

[000004C4]
Stocke searched for Hedge.
{end}

[000004C5]
After Hedge was shown the bloodied
armlet, he decided not to go through
with his plan to betray Garland. {end}

[000004CE]
Due to his displeasure with Dias and
his men, Garland decided to wage
war against Granorg.{end}

[000004CF]

He also expelled his consultant
Hedge because he could not be
trusted.{end}

[000004E2]
The battle at Celestia is about to
begin, with Rosch as the commander.{end}

[000004E3]
The Alistellian army crushed
Granorg and is now preparing
to march on Celestia.{end}

[000004EC]
Elm told Stocke about her friend
Samra who left for Alistel to become
a mediator between Beastkind and
humans, but he never returned.{end}

[00000500]
Stocke took the sword he found in
the underground facility to Elm.
{end}

[00000501]
Elm reinfused Historica with its
powers. It may now be used to slay
Hugo, who has become a demigod.{end}

[00000514]
The long-awaited battle with
Alistel has come. Stocke's party
is ordered to target the enemy
commander.{end}

[00000515]

With their commander slain, the
Alistellian army flees.{end}

[0000051E]
Celestia's joy over their victory
is short-lived. News reaches them
that Cygnus has been wiped out
by Alistel's new weapon.{end}

[00000528]
Gafka taught Stocke how to control
Chi.{end}

[00000532]
Stocke must now find an ally to
replace the annihilated Cygnus army.{end}

[0000053C]
Celestia joined forces with Granorg
and defeated Alistel.
{end}

[0000053D]
But that simply allowed Granorg to
gather their strength. Celestia is
still in peril.{end}

[00000546]
An alliance with Forgia is suggested,
but Gafka seems hesitant, due to the
rift between humans and Beastkind.{end}

[00000547]

However, on seeing Stocke in
possession of the Beast Mark, he
agrees to be an intermediary.{end}

[00000550]
Raul's planned alliance with Forgia
has taken a step towards being
realized.
{end}

[00000551]
Stocke and his party leave to
attempt to forge an alliance.{end}

[0000055A]
The party heads for the wastelands
in the south.
{end}

[0000055B]
After reaching the Itolia Wasteland,
they are told that Forgia lies deep
within Abyssia Forest to the
southeast.{end}

[0000055C]
The party heads east to reach
Abyssia Forest, where Forgia is
hidden.{end}

[00000564]
Stocke's party finally reaches
Forgia. They head to meet with the
Elder to propose the alliance
with Celestia.{end}

[00000582]
A few days after Garland agreed
to aid Eruca, Stocke is summoned
by Garland.{end}

[0000058C]
Garland asks Stocke to protect
Cygnus as Garland goes to meet
with Dias.{end}

[0000058D]
But, Dias sprang a trap at the
meeting, killing Garland.{end}

[00000596]
Garland asked Stocke to protect
Cygnus while the plan to ambush
Dias gets underway.{end}

[000005A0]
Using the information that
Hedge funneled to Dias, Dias
ambushes Garland.{end}

[000005A1]
Stocke returned to the past to
prevent Hedge's betrayal.{end}

[000005AA]
Stocke goes ahead to ambush Dias,
who is waiting in the Itolia Wasteland.{end}

[000005B4]
Dias ordered ballistas constructed.
If they are not destroyed,
the Cygnus army will suffer heavy
losses.{end}

[000005B5]

The party destroyed one ballista,
but another still remained.{end}

[000005B6]
The party destroyed all the
ballistas Dias had positioned
in the southern wastelands.{end}

[000005BE]
Dias deployed barricades to stall
the Cygnus army's advance.{end}

[000005BF]

Garland rushed in with explosives
to rectify the situation.
{end}

[000005C8]
Stocke noticed the ballistas set up on
the northern wasteland. They
needed to be destroyed.
{end}

[000005C9]
The party destroyed one ballista,
but another still remained.{end}

[000005CA]
Stocke's party rushed to rejoin
Garland after destroying the
ballistas in the area.{end}

[000005D2]
Just as Garland planned, Dias'
troops were ravaged by the
whirlwinds.
{end}

[000005D3]
The Executioner Palomides bought
Dias time to escape, and was slain
by Stocke.{end}

[000005DC]
Most of the party felt that if
the leaders of Granorg were
assassinated, the war would end.{end}

[000005DD]

But Aht and Eruca disagreed with
this idea.{end}

[000005DE]
Eruca conviced Stocke to find
other ways to end the war.{end}

[000005E6]
As a condition for the alliance,
Bergas demanded that Stocke
liberate the Gutrals imprisoned in
Skalla.{end}

[000005F0]
Since Skalla must be liberated
before the Gutrals can be freed,
Rosch formulates a plan.{end}

[000005F1]

The party is to disguise themselves
as Alistellian soldiers and
disseminate false information.{end}

[000005F2]
Stocke obtained all the Allistellian
uniforms Rosch needed to begin the
operation.
{end}

[000005FA]
Rosch's plan worked brilliantly, and
Alistel was driven from Skalla.{end}

[000005FB]

The Gutrals agreed to ally with
Stocke and the others.{end}

[00000604]
They learned that the Gutrals'
warrior chief Bergas was also
Gafka's master.
{end}

[0000060E]
In order to liberate Granorg, the
group decided to besiege the Sand
Fortress first.
{end}

[0000060F]
They gathered at Skalla as a prelude
to sieging the Sand Fortress.{end}

[00000618]
Stocke and the party were tasked
with taking down the enemy
commander.{end}

[00000619]
The party successfully took the
commander hostage.
{end}

[00000622]
As Alistellian soldiers fled, some of
the allied forces pursued. Alistel
then used the forbidden weapon,
and turned them into sand.{end}

[00000623]

This weapon must be stopped
somehow.{end}

[0000062C]
Eruca knew that the only way to
defeat the Flux weapon was to use
Granorg's secret treasure, Etherion.{end}

[00000636]
Raul and the others left for Granorg
to sign the peace treaty offered by
Alistel.
{end}

[00000637]
But it was a trap set by Hugo. He
turned Raul and the others into sand.{end}

[00000640]
Without the protection of Etherion,
everyone's Mana will be drained, and
they'll turn to sand.
{end}

[00000641]

But Stocke had obtained Etherion in
a different timeline.{end}

[0000064A]
The party had a way to travel to
Granorg, but a wielder of the Black
Chronicle appeared.{end}

[0000064B]

They defeated the attacker and
were finally able to head to Granorg.{end}

[00000654]
Stocke's party heads to Skalla.
It seems Raynie and Marco know
the way.{end}

[00000655]

Eruca said that someone was waiting
for them there.
{end}

[00000668]
Stocke was reacquainted with the
merchant Tarquin whom he rescued
in Lazvil Hills. Tarquin gave him a
Sand Sword.{end}

[00000672]
The party reached Skalla, and
Eruca told them to head to the inn
to meet the person she spoke of.{end}

[00000673]

The person was a Gutral named
Bergas.{end}

[00000674]
Bergas informed them that
they would need to obtain a
Beast Mark from the
Holff Ruins.{end}

[00000675]

Otherwise, the Gutrals would
not agree to cooperate with
humans.{end}

[0000067C]
Stocke and the party were led into
a lush area by Master Vainqueur's
disciple, Sword.{end}

[00000686]
Stocke and the others depart in
search of the Beast Mark, which
can be found in the Holff Ruins
hidden deep in Abyssia Forest.{end}

[00000687]

It seems the Holff Ruins are to the
north of this forest.{end}

[00000690]
The party passed through Abyssia
Forest and reached Holff Ruins. The
Beast Mark is somewhere within.
{end}

[0000069A]
Stocke's party completed the trial
and obtained the Beast Mark. An
alliance with Forgia can now be
formed.{end}

[000006A4]
The party heads to Granorg while
the Gutrals gather. They easily
enter the palace.{end}

[000006A5]

However, this was a trap set by
Dias.{end}

[000006AE]
Now that the Gutrals have agreed
to help, the party will finally begin
making their assault on Granorg.{end}

[000006B8]
The castle gates are sealed, and
breaking through will be difficult.
If only the Resistance was around
to help...{end}

[000006B9]

Will died in battle, but if he had had
the means to fight, perhaps he and
Otto might live.{end}

[000006BA]
It seems that Pierre needs to protect
something important to him to avoid
making a mistake. Whatever it is,
it should be in the city...{end}

[000006BB]

Will, Pierre, and Otto helped the
party successfully enter Granorg.{end}

[000006C2]
Stocke heads straight for the
palace. His destination is the throne
room, and Protea.
{end}

[000006C3]
Dias and Selvan escape from
Stocke's offensive. Eruca takes back
the throne, returning power to
the royal family.{end}

[000006C4]
The treasure, Etherion, had been
stolen by Protea, but was returned
to Eruca.
{end}

[000006C5]
Eruca gives Etherion to Stocke,
saying that he has more need of
it than she does.{end}

[000006CC]
The final battle to take back
Granorg was about to begin.
{end}

[000006CD]
But Hugo had a problem and is
unable to use Divine Judgement.
{end}

[000006D6]
Now bearing Etherion, Stocke and
the others begin their advance
toward Granorg.
{end}

[000006D7]
After entering Granorg, the party
heads for the underground waterway
that will let them access the palace.
{end}

[000006D8]
The party made their way through
Granorg and found the waterway
behind the bar. These tunnels will
let them sneak into the palace.{end}

[000006E0]
The party entered the palace
and stopped the Flux weapon,
then hurried to rejoin Rosch.{end}

[000006E1]
The court knight Dias was ready
to flee the kingdom. He was slain
by Stocke and the party.{end}

[000006E2]
Hugo speaks to the public to
calm the citizenry, but it is
discovered that Noah is no
longer alive.{end}

[000006EA]
Field Marshal Viola decides to
take responsibility for the Alistel
army's actions, and lets Stocke
slay her.{end}

[000006F4]
It seems Hugo returned to Alistel
after fleeing Granorg Palace.
Stocke heads to Alistel.{end}

[000006F5]

Hugo is in trouble after being
abandoned by Selvan and Heiss.{end}

[000006F6]
Hugo escaped into the facility
under Alistel. He enlisted Fennel's
help in taking up a forbidden power.{end}

[000006FE]
General Hugo gained Flux powers
and became a demigod. Hugo offers
Stocke the opportunity to join his side.{end}

[00000708]
Stocke accepts Hugo's proposition,
but is swallowed by the tremendous
power of Flux.{end}

[00000712]
Hugo is able to restore himself
using the power of Flux to rewind
time. He can't be wounded at all.
{end}

[00000713]
Fennel, on the verge of death,
tells Stocke of a Celestian blade
that could cancel Flux.
{end}

[00000714]
The blade's power has already been
lost. The Satyros in Celestia may be
able to restore it.{end}

[00000715]

Historica's power has been
restored, and it cancels out
Hugo's Flux abilities.{end}

[0000071C]
The demigod Hugo was slain
with the power of Historica.
The long war is finally over.{end}

[0000071D]
Peace has finally been returned
to the continent, and a new
reign of peace will begin.{end}

[00000726]
Peace is returning to Granorg
under Eruca's reign. But someone
remains, lurking in the shadow of
history...{end}

[00000730]
Heiss invaded Granorg's Royal Hall
and sealed it with the power of Flux
in order to stop Eruca from
performing the ritual.{end}

[00000731]

Heiss tells Stocke to come to the
Imperial Ruins.{end}

[0000073A]
Heiss says he wants to destroy the
world, as it is not worth saving...
and that he had brought up Stocke
to usher in the destruction.{end}

[0000073B]

Heiss also says he and Stocke are
one and the same.{end}

[00000744]
It is revealed that Stocke and Heiss
are both Sacrifices for the Ritual
of Flux.
{end}

[00000745]
Heiss was the late King Victor's
younger brother, and escaped his
fate by defecting to Alistel.{end}

[00000746]
The next Sacrifice was the older
prince, Ernst. Heiss kidnapped Ernst
and erased his memories of his past,
giving him a new name... Stocke.{end}

[0000074E]
Heiss tells Stocke to join him, as they
are both Sacrifices who have been
forsaken by the world. Stocke
declines.{end}

[0000074F]

Heiss escapes after losing the
battle, but swears to kill Eruca
before she meets Stocke.{end}

[00000750]
What time did Heiss escape to?
When did Stocke and Eruca meet
for the first time?{end}

[0000078A]
Heiss fails to assassinate Eruca.
He moves in time and space and
invades Granorg's Royal Hall.
{end}

[0000078B]
Stocke pursues Heiss to the Royal
Hall. The final battle over the
chronicles begins...{end}

[00000794]
Heiss' minions get in the party's way,
but Garland takes them on and
protects Stocke.{end}

[0000079E]
As the party hurries to Eruca, they
reach a hall containing bizarre
floating boulders.
{end}

[000007B2]
The path to continue on has been
blocked. It seems the four sources
of black energy sealing the way
must be removed.{end}

[000007BC]
Stocke defeated Executioner
Palomides, who had been turned
into a black guardian, and released
the first source of black energy.{end}

[000007C6]
Stocke defeated King Garland the
Mighty, who had been turned into a
black guardian, and released the
second source of black energy.{end}

[000007D0]
Stocke defeated the giant spider at
Holff Ruins, which had been turned
into a black guardian, and released
the third source of black energy.{end}

[000007DA]
Stocke defeated Field Marshal Viola,
the Valkyrie, who had been turned
into a black guardian, and released
the last source of black energy.{end}

[000007EE]
Stocke saved the unconscious
Eruca from Dias. Selvan had been
with him, but seems to have headed
to the Royal Hall with Heiss.{end}

[000007EF]

Dias and Selvan, enticed by Heiss,
met short ends.{end}

[000007F8]
The final battle against Heiss is
about to begin. Stocke tells Lippti
and Teo of his resolution and heads
to the Royal Hall.{end}

[00000802]
Heiss, who had absorbed the souls of
countless people, faces off against
Stocke.
{end}

[00000803]
But Stocke, his strength amplified
by his grim determination, proved
to be even stronger than Heiss.
{end}

[00000804]
Heiss realizes that his only option
left is to breach the power of Flux
and destroy the world.{end}

[0000080C]
After the fighting ended, Rosch
became the general of the Alistel
army. He then married Sonja.
{end}

[00000816]
After a fierce battle, Heiss meets
his end. Stocke's party returns to the
present time.
{end}

[00000817]
But if the breach in Flux isn't
stopped, the world will die. The
ritual of Flux is required...{end}

[00000818]
Eruca attempts the ritual without
using her brother Stocke's soul.
{end}

[00000819]
But without a Sacrifice's soul, the
ritual fails. Eruca collapses before
the power of Flux.{end}

[0000081A]
Stocke speaks with Eruca and gives
his soul to her.{end}

[0000081B]
Stocke says his farewells, but
everyone believes they will meet
again. The ritual of Flux succeeds,
and peace returns to the world.{end}

[00000820]
Field Marshal Viola miraculously
survived the battle. She gazes upon
a peaceful world, even while fighting
against the disease within her.{end}

[0000082A]
After overcoming her sadness, Eruca
continues the ritual as a true queen.
The strength she received from her
brother is evident in her strong gaze.{end}

[00000834]
After parting with Stocke, Aht gained
a newfound awareness of her role as
a shaman and traveled the land in
order to protect the world he saved.{end}

[00000848]
"What is true strength?" Gafka asks
the next generation.
{end}

[00000849]
Gafka was a master of martial
arts, but he had seen the inner
strength within Stocke's spirit.{end}

[00000852]
While everyone else celebrated the
end of the fighting, Raynie was
different.
{end}

[00000853]
She continues to wait for Stocke's
return, in order to keep the promise
she had made.


{end}

[0000085C]
Marco lost many people he knew
in the war.
{end}

[0000085D]
He feels that it is his duty as a
survivor of the violence to protect
the peace that so many had died for.

{end}

[00000866]
Lippti and Teo had watched over
the history of civilization in Historia
since the fall of the empire.{end}

[00000867]

The two of them will surely continue
to watch over the world.

{end}

[0000087A]
Love can be created by coming
together and through true
communication.
{end}

[0000087B]
This relationship will surely change
the way humanity and the Beastkind
see each other.


{end}

[00000884]
Behind every heroic act stands the
hard work of countless people who
go unrecognized by history.
{end}

[00000885]
The efforts of the Resistance that
supported Eruca will live on in
people's memories.

{end}

[0000088E]
Rosch visits the graves of the men
he lost at Gran Plain. Sonja, his
longtime friend, goes with him.{end}

[0000088F]
Rosch and Sonja vow to keep the
world safe, for the sake of Stocke
and the others who died.{end}

[00000890]
But Kiel, along with the men Rosch
thought had perished, appeared there.
{end}

[00000891]
Kiel explained that a kind traveler
had saved them. From Kiel's
description, Rosch is reminded of
only one person...{end}

[00000892]
Rosch is certain that he will meet
this traveler again, the man who
is his best friend...{end}

[00000898]
An Alistellian soldier wants two
Anti-Sleeps in order to stay awake
on duty.{end}

[00000899]

Stocke gave the soldier a couple of
Anti-Sleeps.{end}

[000008A2]
A soldier at Alistel Castle said he
would teach Marco skills in exchange
for martial arts scrolls.
{end}

[000008A3]
Marco learned Right Assault from
the Right-Cut Scroll.{end}

[000008A4]
Marco learned Left Assault from the
Left-Cut Scroll.{end}

[000008A5]
Marco learned Sleep Cloud from the
Sleep Gas Scroll.{end}

[000008A6]
Marco learned Spin Slash from the
Roll-Cut Scroll.
{end}

[000008A7]
And so, Marco learned all the skills
that the soldier had to offer him.
{end}

[000008AC]
A soldier at Alistel Castle said he
would teach Raynie skills in exchange
for martial arts scrolls.
{end}

[000008AD]
Raynie learned Resist Boost from
the Darkshield Scroll.
{end}

[000008AE]
Raynie learned Sleep Break from
the Slumbering Scroll.
{end}

[000008AF]
Raynie learned Armor Break from
the Piercing Scroll.
{end}

[000008B0]
Raynie learned Poison Blast from
the Poisoner's Scroll.
{end}

[000008B1]
And so, Raynie learned all the skills
that the soldier had to offer her.{end}

[000008B6]
Excellent soldiers are always in
demand in Alistel.{end}

[000008B7]

Stocke is requested to recruit
the mercenaries staying at the
Alistel Inn.{end}

[000008B8]
Stocke speaks with the pair of
mercenaries at the inn. He checks
if they intend to join the Alistel
army.{end}

[000008B9]

When Stocke goes to Alistel Castle,
he learns that the pair have joined
the army.{end}

[000008C0]
Stock was asked to recruit Berman,
who works at the Alma Mine.
{end}

[000008C1]
Just as informed, Berman was at the
Alma Mine. He seemed intrigued by
the job offer.{end}

[000008C2]
Berman joined the Alistel army. He
excels in handling explosive materials.{end}

[000008CA]
A gladiator named Gadeff is said to
be the most powerful fighter in
Cygnus.
{end}

[000008CB]
If he joins the Alistel army, it would
be a boon to the armed forces. Stock
has been asked to recruit this man.{end}

[000008CC]
Gadeff was the gladiator using Chi
who handles the city's battle
tournaments. He gladly accepts
Stocke's request.{end}

[000008CD]

The Alistel army will surely be
stronger with this talented warrior
in the ranks.{end}

[000008D4]
A mercenary by the name of Ditto
is in the town of Skalla. Stocke's
newest task is to recruit this man.
{end}

[000008D5]
Ditto had already joined the
Granorg army and died in battle.
Could he have been stopped?{end}

[000008D6]
Stocke returned to the past and
spoke with the merchant Tarquin,
asking him to suggest Ditto not join
Granorg's army.{end}

[000008D7]

This proved successful, and Ditto
was waiting in Skalla. He said he would
fight for Alistel.{end}

[000008D8]
Ditto was successfully hired to fight
for Alistel. He is a trustworthy man
with an extremely high degree of
professionalism.{end}

[000008DE]
As the party pursues the fleeing
Hugo, an old man appears before
them.
{end}

[000008DF]
He asks Stocke to save his friend,
who was one of Fennel's Gauntlet test
subjects in the underground facility.{end}

[000008E0]
Stocke defeats a thautomaton in the
facility below Alistel. They discover
it was once the man who was being
used as the Gauntlet test subject.{end}

[000008E1]

The old man thanks Stocke.{end}

[000008E8]
Anna of Alistel asks Stocke to find
a replica of Eruca's ring.{end}

[000008E9]
He searches for a ring in Granorg,
but they are so popular that he
cannot get his hands on one.{end}

[000008EA]
Stocke speaks with Eruca. She
requests that he give Anna Eruca's
own ring.{end}

[000008EB]

Stocke secretly gave Anna the ring
that actually belonged to Eruca.
Anna was ecstatic.{end}

[000008F2]
Eruca stays on the battlefield for
the sake of Granorg. She is slain in
battle, but her ideals are passed on
by her comrades.{end}

[000008FC]
Stocke is asked by some young
children in Alistel to help their
father.
{end}

[000008FD]
The father was a botanist. He tells
Stocke that he wants to learn how to
grow Conuts, the specialty of
Cornet Village.{end}

[000008FE]
Stocke finds out how to grow Conuts
by asking around Cornet Village.
{end}

[000008FF]
After learning that the botanist
will use his research for military
purposes, Stocke declines
cooperating with him.{end}

[00000900]
Lippti and Teo appeared and
indicated that this research
could be used for peace.
{end}

[00000901]
Stocke goes back in time and
meets with the botanist, this
time convincing him to use his
research for good.{end}

[00000906]
The botanist's research is used by
the Alistel military, causing the
desertification of the continent
to become even more severe.{end}

[00000910]
Many fall victim to mudslides that
commonly occur on Lazvil Hill after
heavy rains.{end}

[00000911]

Stocke uses the skill he learned
from Tarquin to destroy boulders
and rescue a trapped man.{end}

[0000091A]
A young cook in Granorg aims to
become the world's best chef.
{end}

[0000091B]
To make his ultimate dish, Great Boar
steak with Cornet sauce, he asks
Stocke to bring boar meat from
Lazvil Hills.{end}

[0000091C]
Gathering the ingredients proves
difficult. Each one has a different
time when they are best used in the
dish.{end}

[0000091D]

Stocke prepares the food in the
best way possible. The ultimate
dish has been completed!{end}

[00000924]
Meese in Alistel says that Sonja
has been acting strangely. He asks
Stocke to check on her and lend
help as necessary.{end}

[00000925]

Sonja was troubled about Rosch's
odd behavior lately.{end}

[00000926]
Rosch couldn't bring himself to tell
Sonja how he feels about her.
Stocke gives Rosch some advice.{end}

[00000927]

Meese is relieved that Sonja is
acting normal again, and asks
Stocke to look after her.{end}

[0000092E]
Rosch and Sonja never
expressed their true feelings.
Rosch later lost his life on
the battlefield.{end}

[00000938]
Stocke spoke with a woman admiring
flowers in the hall of Alistel
Castle, and learned of a special
flower.{end}

[00000939]

This flower is the Celestia Iris. The
woman asks Stocke to bring her one if
he finds any.{end}

[0000093A]
Stocke succeeds in obtaining a
young Celestia Iris plant.{end}

[0000093B]
The Celestia Iris is a fragile flower,
and it will not bloom if planted at the
wrong time.{end}

[0000093C]
Stocke returned to the woman at the
perfect time to grow the Celestia
Iris, and gave her the seedling.{end}

[00000942]
To help Cedric of Alistel write a book,
Stocke goes to speak with Viola at
the Sand Fortress.{end}

[00000943]
Viola agrees to help Stocke but asks
him to return some other time.{end}

[00000944]
Viola entrusts her diary to Stocke
and tells him to put it to good use.
{end}

[00000945]
Stocke showed Viola's diary to
Cedric, who promised not to reveal
the diary to the public unless it
becomes necessary.{end}

[0000094C]
Cedric goes missing. Afterwards, Hugo
becomes the ruler of Alistel, and his
ambitions go out of control.{end}

[00000956]
Stocke is called over by a
Granorgite soldier, who asks Stocke
to bring the traveling entertainer
Liese to him.{end}

[00000957]

Liese declines the offer to meet the
man, but it seems he cannot forget
about Liese.{end}

[00000958]
Stock reunites with Liese in Abyssia
Forest. He tells her that the man had
followed her and entered the forest.{end}

[00000959]

The man was attacked by beasts and
died. Liese is shocked when Stocke
shows her his letter.{end}

[0000095A]
Stocke went back in time to show the
letter to Liese, convincing her to
meet the man. She believes Stocke
despite the odd circumstances.{end}

[00000960]
Liese and the man ended up never
meeting each other. This incident
causes a war to break out between
the humans and Beastkind.{end}

[0000096A]
Kaizan at the Granorg inn asks
Stocke to obtain a special paint. It
seems the man who makes it died in
Alma Mine.{end}

[0000096B]

Stocke meets the paint creator, but
Kaizan had bought the last of it and
went to Alistel.{end}

[0000096C]
Stocke meets Kaizan in Alistel. He
asks the artist to spare some paint,
but he refuses. Stocke returns to
Granorg.{end}

[0000096D]

In Granorg, Kaizan gave Stocke his
unfinished painting.{end}

[0000096E]
Stocke shows Kaizan the art that he
would paint in the other timeline.
Kaizan is so moved by this piece
that he shares his paint with Stocke.{end}

[0000096F]

Stocke returns to Kaizan with the
paint to complete his art.{end}

[00000974]
The boy outside the weapon shop in
Alistel was troubled.
{end}

[00000975]
He believed that his father would not
return from the Sand Fortress
because he did not have his lucky
charm. Stocke promises to deliver it.{end}

[00000976]
Stocke returns to the past and gives
the father his charm. The father
gives Stocke a letter to give to
his son.{end}

[00000977]

Stocke gave the boy his father's
letter. The boy was determined to
become stronger.{end}

[0000097E]
The man raising opposition against
Protea's rule in Granorg died. But did
his death have any repercussions?{end}

[0000097F]

Stocke returns to the past, meets
with the man, and demonstrated
his recklessness.{end}

[00000980]
The man decided to make his fight
against the government a
philosophical one by writing books.
He thanks Stocke for the advice. {end}

[00000988]
As Granorg burns, Stock meets a man
who claims the Rose Sword is a family
heirloom and belongs to him.{end}

[00000989]

The Alistellian soldier says Dias took
the sword from him while he was
injured.{end}

[0000098A]
Dias seems to meet Selvan downtown
often. If Stocke could approach him
then...
{end}

[0000098B]
Stocke corners Dias at the downtown
inn, but Selvan takes a hostage.
Stocke takes the Rose Sword and
escapes.{end}

[0000098C]
Stocke meets with the soldier again
and gives him the Rose Sword. The
man thanks Stocke for managing to
complete such a dangerous task.{end}

[00000992]
Dias notes Stocke's skills and hires
him as an assassin. But this bloody
path could not save the world...{end}

[0000099C]
Stocke meets a woman in Alistel who
lost her husband to disease. If he'd
had an Anti-Poison, he could have
been saved...{end}

[0000099D]

Stocke went to the past to give an
Anti-Poison to the man.{end}

[0000099E]
The medicine saved the man's
life before he could die of
poison.{end}

[000009A6]
Vanoss worries about Aht as he
leaves Alistel. It seems the previous
shaman had strayed from her path....{end}

[000009A7]

Vanoss hoped that Aht wouldn't
make the same mistake.{end}

[000009A8]
Stocke hears that the previous
shaman was supposedly in Skalla.
{end}

[000009A9]
They meet the shaman. Aht quietly
returns the shaman's friend's soul
to the heavens.{end}

[000009AA]
Vanoss reveals that the previous
shaman was his daughter. He thanks
Stocke for helping to return her to
the right path.{end}

[000009B0]
Aht uses her shamanistic powers as
she sees fit, and imprisons Stocke
somewhere to protect him.{end}

[000009BA]
After fleeing to Celestia, Sonja
says that the Gauntlet can be
strengthened with items called
Cores.{end}

[000009BB]

The Impale Core allows Rosch to use
Impale Mode.
{end}

[000009BC]
With the Blast Core, Rosch can now
use Blasting Pain.
{end}

[000009BD]
The Haste Core gives Rosch the
ability to use Haste Mode.
{end}

[000009BE]
With all three Cores, Rosch's
Gauntlet is now the most powerful
it can be.
{end}

[000009C4]
There may be a spy in the city...
or so Ricky says. If this is true,
something must be done.{end}

[000009C5]
Stocke meets a woman named Mimel
at a bar. It seems she and Marco are
friends.{end}

[000009C6]
Stocke questioned the barkeep and
finds evidence that Mimel is some
kind of spy.
{end}

[000009C7]
The party confronts Mimel with the
evidence and stops her from further
spying. However, someone turns her
into sand.{end}

[000009C8]
Stocke reports to Ricky regarding
the spy. Who was behind this? With
Mimel dead, any answers to that
question have been lost.{end}

[000009CE]
Mimel takes her own life after being
sent to prison by Stocke. Learning
this drivesMarco into a murderous
frenzy.{end}

[000009D8]
In order to meet with a mysterious
martial artist in Itolia Wasteland,
Stocke must search for his disciples.{end}

[000009D9]

"Time carries away all things. The
past shapes the future. Hope is in
the past."{end}

[000009DA]
Stocke met with the disciple,
Chalice, in Celestia, and found the
location of the Pact she had hidden.{end}

[000009DB]

Stocke learned the location of
another Pact by speaking with
Pentacle in Granorg.{end}

[000009DC]
Stocke found the fourth disciple,
Wand, in Alistel, and learned the
location of the pact.{end}

[000009DD]

After taking all the Pacts to Sword,
Master Vainqueur appeared before
Stocke.{end}

[000009E2]
The Gutrals' secret.
{end}

[000009EC]
Galva of Forgia shows Gafka how to
become the legendary Beast God.
{end}

[000009ED]
To do so, the "Beast God's Nail" is
required. It seems it was last seen at
Gran Plain...{end}

[000009EE]
The Gutral warrior's tomb seems to
be at Gran Plain.{end}

[000009EF]
Stocke's party went to the tomb. The
Gutral's spirit appeared and gave
them the "Beast God's Nail."
{end}

[000009F0]
Stocke gives Galva the "Beast God's
Nail." Galva tells Stocke to come talk
to him when he's ready.
{end}

[000009F1]

Gafka decides not to throw away his
heart to gain power. Galva seems
pleased by this.{end}

[000009F6]
Bergas of Forgia promises to train
Gafka if he brings Gutral books.
{end}

[000009F7]
Gafka learned Musou from the
Strongman Book.
{end}

[000009F8]
Gafka learned Triple Strike from the
Tristrike Book.
{end}

[000009F9]
Gafka learned Wind God Strike from
the Wind God Book.
{end}

[000009FA]
Gafka learned Cosmos from the
Omnipedia.
{end}

[000009FB]
And so, Gafka learned all the skills
Bergas had to train him.
{end}

[00000A00]
Gafka became the Beast God and saw
all humans as his enemies. He uses
his power to eliminate them and
wipes the world clean of humanity.{end}

[00000A0A]
Immediately before the capturing
of the Sand Fortress, Marco tells
Stocke that Raynie has been acting
odd.{end}

[00000A0B]

Stocke met with Raynie. She tells him
of the feeling she had been hiding
all this time.{end}

[00000A0C]
This journey cannot be ended. That
would cause the world's downfall.
{end}

[00000A0D]
Stocke tells Marco that Raynie will
be all right. Their journey to save
the world will not be ended
prematurely.{end}

[00000A14]
Stocke chose to live his life with
Raynie. He and Raynie quietly sit
together and watch the world's end.{end}

[00000A1E]
Garland asks that Stocke recover
his armlet, which was lost in Itolia
Wasteland.{end}

[00000A1F]

Just as he was told, Stocke was able
to find the armlet in Itolia
Wasteland.{end}

[00000A20]
With his armlet returned, Garland
tells Stocke about it.
{end}

[00000A21]
He had always kept this armlet
during his gladiator days. The armlet
is a reminder of those times.{end}

[00000A28]
Stocke is reunited with Bram of the
Desert Crows in Cygnus, but Bram
doesn't seem as determined as he
once did.{end}

[00000A29]

The countless defeats have eaten
away at his spirit. Can he make a
comeback?{end}

[00000A2A]
A boy who had been saved by Bram
in the past lives in Alistel. The boy
tells Stocke how he idolizes Bram.
{end}

[00000A2B]

In Granorg, there is a boy who looks
up to Bram as a chivalrous robber.
{end}

[00000A2C]
Stocke tells Bram of the children
who look up to him. Bram's spirits are
lifted by these words.{end}

[00000A32]
Master Vainqueur says that he will
teach skills to Stocke in exchange
for Sword Pacts.
{end}

[00000A33]
Stocke learned Shadow Arts after
returning the Shade Pact.
{end}

[00000A34]
Stocke learned Dullahan Sword from
the Death Pact.
{end}

[00000A35]
Stocke learned Will o' Wisp from the
Fire Pact.
{end}

[00000A36]
Stocke learned Wraith Blade from the
Soul Pact.
{end}

[00000A37]
Stocke learned all the skills Master
Vainqueur had to teach him.
{end}

[00000A3C]
Master Vainqueur says that he will
teach skills to Aht in exchange
for Star Pacts.
{end}

[00000A3D]
Aht learned Dancing Death from
the Meteorite Pact.
{end}

[00000A3E]
Aht learned Volt Star Trap from the
Thunderstar Pact.
{end}

[00000A3F]
Aht learned Flame Star Trap from
the Firestar Pact.
{end}

[00000A40]
Aht learned Frost Star Trap from the
Icestar Pact.
{end}

[00000A41]
Aht learned all the skills that Master
Vainqueur had to teach her.
{end}

[00000A46]
Master Vainqueur says that he will
teach skills to Eruca in exchange
for Light Pacts.
{end}

[00000A47]
Eruca learned Shine from the
Sunlight Pact.
{end}

[00000A48]
Eruca learned Burst Light from the
Firelight Pact.
{end}

[00000A49]
Eruca learned Divine Light from the
Protection Pact.
{end}

[00000A4A]
Eruca learned Holy Light from the
Divine Pact.
{end}

[00000A4B]
Eruca learned all the skills that
Master Vainqueur had to teach her.
{end}

[00000A50]
Master Vainqueur brings on the final
ordeal for the students who learned
all his skills.{end}

[00000A51]

That is... they must defeat him. What
happens after the Master is
defeated?{end}

[00000A52]
After a fierce battle,
Stocke and the others emerged
victorious.
{end}

[00000A53]
After praising them, Master
Vainqueur re-forges Historica
and returns it to its original
form.{end}

[00000A5A]
Stocke meets an engineer in Alistel's
underground laboratory.
{end}

[00000A5B]
This man says that Fennel used to
research Gauntlets, but suddenly
stopped. Perhaps Stocke may learn
more in the other timeline.{end}

[00000A5C]
Stocke returned to the past and
spoke with Fennel. Fennel presents
Stocke with new technology to be
used with Gauntlets.{end}

[00000A64]
Stocke meets a man in Granorg who
had been severely injured by falling
rocks. If he hadn't been there...{end}

[00000A65]

Stocke goes to the past and warns
the man, but it seems he refuses to
listen...{end}

[00000A66]
After returning to the future,
the man is still injured. But he
remembers Stocke from when he
attempted to warn the man...{end}

[00000A6E]
The final opponent the gladiator
had prepared was a giant spider,
like the one that attacked Cygnus.{end}

[00000A6F]

Stocke was somehow able to slay
this monster, and his name became
well known in Cygnus.{end}
