:0000003E:

[00000001]
You removed the barricade,
went south and safely returned
to Alistel.{end}

[00000002]
You obtained an Alma Gummy
and gave it to Sonja.{end}

[00000003]
In order to move on in the
other timeline, you obeyed
Heiss' new order.{end}

[00000004]
You decided to go with Rosch and
became his second-in-command.{end}

[00000005]
You saved a merchant in the
other timeline and delivered
the bombs to Alma Mine.{end}

[00000006]
You brought Mondol a Sharp Claw
and he taught you how to find
wood.{end}

[00000007]
You gave Mondol a Pickaxe, and
he taught you how to dig for
ore.{end}

[00000008]
You rescued the bomb merchant
from the Desert Crow's attack.{end}

[00000009]
You defeated the goblin at
Lazvil Hill and got the
Goblin Stone.{end}

[0000000A]
Having learned sword dancing
from Kiel, you were able to
get past the checkpoint.{end}

[0000000B]
You started a fire from the
wood you found and set up camp
at Gran Plain.{end}

[0000000C]
You found the entrance to the
sewers beneath the tavern.{end}

[0000000D]
You saved Claire in the sewers.
She gave you a bag as thanks.{end}

[0000000E]
You used Silence, which you
learned from Heiss, to pass
the guards.{end}

[0000000F]
Claire, the girl from the
sewer, helped Pierre come to
his senses.{end}

[00000010]
You gave Will the Sand Sword
that you got in Skalla.{end}

[00000011]
You avoided fighting an
injured Rosch bu giving him a
chance to recover.{end}

[00000012]
You defeated the Qi-using
fighter and learned that Eruca
is being held in the castle.{end}

[00000013]
You defeated the lizard-rider
and proved your strength to
Cygnus.{end}

[00000014]
Your second opponent was the
Desert Crow, who you had
defeated at Lazvil Hill.{end}

[00000015]
After learning about Qi from
Gafka, you defeated Cygnus'
stongest warrior.{end}

[00000016]
Defeating the monster from the
Abyssal Forest garnered you
even more fame in Cygnus.{end}

[00000017]
You have overcome the strongest
monster in the gladatorial
contests. Well done!{end}

[00000018]
Showing Hedge the Bloodied
Armlet prevented him from
going over to Dias' side.{end}

[00000019]
After giving them the Goblin
Stone, you gained their trust.
Try visiting their village now.{end}

[0000001A]
You obtained the Beast Mark
and formed an alliance withe
the Gutrals.{end}

[0000001B]
Will, Otto, and Pierre...
The three Resistance leaders
opened Granorg's front gate.{end}

[0000001C]
You saved Eruca from her
assailant at Gran Plains.{end}

[0000001D]
Having learned Search Eye from
Aht, you disposed of all the
bombs.{end}

[0000001E]
You gave the Secret Document
to Field Marshal Viola, and
she devised a plan.{end}

[0000001F]
You and Sonja repaired
Rosch's Gauntlet.{end}

[00000020]
You defeated the monster at
Lazvil Hills and saved Vanoss.{end}

[00000021]
Alistel's military invasion,
led by General Hugo, has no
indication of stopping.{end}

[00000022]
With Rosch's help, you defeated
the Alistel officer and fended
off the army.{end}

[00000023]
Seeing the Beast Mark, Gafka
hesitates no more.
To Forgia!{end}

[00000024]
Gakfa guided you through the
Abyssal Forest and took you
to Forgia.{end}

[00000025]
You found Samra's sword beneath
Alistel and had Elm repair it.{end}

[00000026]
The mission was a success.
You freed Skalla with a
minimum of bloodshed.{end}

[00000027]
You gave Eruca the Etherion
you got from Protea.{end}

[00000028]
You snuck beneath Granorg and
stopped Alistel's weapon.{end}

[00000029]
The Historica was returned to
its full strength, and you
used it to defeat Hugo.{end}

[0000002A]
A violent clash occurred at
the Imperial Ruins.{end}

[0000002B]
Stocke mastered the technique
Shadow Arts.{end}

[0000002C]
Stocke mastered the magic
Will-o' Wisp.{end}

[0000002D]
Stocke mastered the technique
Dullahan Sword.{end}

[0000002E]
Stocke mastered the technique
Wraith Blade.{end}

[0000002F]
Eruca mastered the magic
Burst Light.{end}

[00000030]
Eruca mastered the magic
Divine Light.{end}

[00000031]
Eruca mastered the magic
Holy Light.{end}

[00000032]
Eruca mastered the magic
Shine.{end}

[00000033]
Aht mastered the magic
Lightning Star Position.{end}

[00000034]
Aht mastered the magic
Flame Star Position.{end}

[00000035]
Aht mastered the magic
Ice Star Position.{end}

[00000036]
Aht mastered the technique
Dancing Star.{end}

[00000037]
Gafka mastered the technique
Musou.{end}

[00000038]
Gafka mastered the magic
Cosmos{end}

[00000039]
Gafka mastered the technique
Sougeki{end}

[0000003A]
Gafka mastered the technique
Wind God Fist.{end}

[0000003B]
Rosch mastered the technique
Impale Mode.{end}

[0000003C]
Rosch mastered the technique
Blast Mode.{end}

[0000003D]
Rosch mastered the technique
Haste Mode.{end}

[000000C7]
This event doesn't occur.{end}
