:0000003E:

[00000001]
It's too dangerous to fight
Palomides. You can't use the
northern path.{end}

[00000002]
Special measures are required
to obtain the Alma Gummy
Sonja wants.{end}

[00000003]
Heiss is your mentor and direct
superior. He seems to have new
orders for you...{end}

[00000004]
Your friend Rosch wants your
help in forming a new unit.{end}

[00000005]
The merchant who is supposed
to deliver a bomb to Alma Mine
is missing. Could he be saved?{end}

[00000006]
Mondol at Lazvil Hills is
trying to tell you something.
It seems you need a Sharp Claw...{end}

[00000007]
Mondol at Alma Mine is trying
to tell you something. It seems
you need a Pickaxe...{end}

[00000008]
The merchant who is to deliver
a bomb to the Rosch Brigade
went missing at Lazvil Hills.{end}

[00000009]
A goblin is rumored to appear
in Lazvil Hills. What is it
doing there...?{end}

[0000000A]
In order to pass Granorg's
checkpoint, you need to perform
a trick. Can you dance?{end}

[0000000B]
You will need to use Search Eye
to find dry wood before setting
camp at Gran Plain.{end}

[0000000C]
There has to be a secret way
into the castle... Search the
entire city.{end}

[0000000D]
You ran into a little girl in
the sewers. Take her back to
the surface.{end}

[0000000E]
The security for Granorg Palace
is air-tight... In order to get
past, you need special skills.{end}

[0000000F]
Pierre betrayed Eruca for his
little sister's sake...
But what does Claire want?{end}

[00000010]
Will, one of the leaders of the
Resistance, is looking for a
Sand Sword to use in battle.{end}

[00000011]
Rosch has strayed from his
path. You must do something in
the other timeline to help him.{end}

[00000012]
In order to learn Eruca's
whereabouts, you must defeat
the broker's brother in combat.{end}

[00000013]
You entered the fighting
tournament. Who will your
first opponent be?{end}

[00000014]
Your next opponent in the
tournament looks like a strong
warrior.{end}

[00000015]
This is a vital moment.
Defeat this for to learn where
Eruca is being held.{end}

[00000016]
Your next opponent is
apparently is coming from
afar. Wait until he arrives.{end}

[00000017]
Your final foe is a terrifying
monster... Stocke, be careful.{end}

[00000018]
Hedge, exiled by Garland...
You must stop him before he
meets Dias.{end}

[00000019]
The goblins at the Itolia
Wasteland are looking for the
Goblin Stone, lost long ago...{end}

[00079695]
Meaning of the Beast Mark{end}

[0000001B]
You may break through the
gates of Granorg Palace with
the Resistance's help.{end}

[0000001C]
It seems someone is trying to
keep you from meeting Eruca
again. Don't give up!{end}

[0000001D]
The Sand Fortress can be saved
if you can remove the invisible
bombs. But how...?{end}

[0000001E]
You got a Secret Document
mentioning an attack on Rosch.
You should show it to someone.{end}

[0000001F]
Rosch is injured and has lost
his spirit... Sonja must be
the key in helping him recover.{end}

[00000020]
A monster appeared in Lazvil
Hills. Defeat it for the sake
of the Celestians.{end}

[00000021]
Alistel defeated Granorg.
What is going on in that
country...?{end}

[00000022]
Alistel's assault on Celestia
has intensified. Fend them off
with Rosch.{end}

[00000023]
Gafka thinks you should go to
Forgia. You do have the
Beast Mark...{end}

[00000024]
Hopefully you can get Forgia's
assistance in fighting
Alistel...{end}

[00000025]
Samra, Elm's friend, has
disappeared with the Celestian
sword in Alistel.{end}

[00000026]
Free the captured Gutral at
Skalla to gain the trust of
the Gutral.{end}

[00000027]
You need the Granorg treasure,
Etherion, to stop the Flux
weapon. However...{end}

[00000028]
With Etherion, you should be
able to stop the Flux weapon.{end}

[00000029]
Hugo has become an immortal.
To defeat him, you must restore
the power of the sword...{end}

[0000002A]
............
It seems something awaits you
at the Imperial Ruins...{end}

[0000002B]
Give the Shade Pact to the
goblin to teach Stocke the
technique Shadow Arts.{end}

[0000002C]
Give the Death Pact to the
goblin to teach Stocke the
magic Will o' Wisp.{end}

[0000002D]
Give the Fire Pact to the
goblin to teach Stocke the
technique Dullahan Sword.{end}

[0000002E]
Give the Soul Pact to the
goblin to teach Stocke the
technique Wraith Blade.{end}

[0000002F]
Give the Sunlight Pact to the
goblin to teach Eruca the
magic Burst Light.{end}

[00000030]
Give the Firelight Pact to the
goblin to teach Eruca the
magic Divine Light.{end}

[00000031]
Give the Protection Pact to the
goblin to teach Eruca the
magic Holy Light.{end}

[00000032]
Give the Divine Pact to the
goblin to teach Eruca the
magic Shine.{end}

[00000033]
Give the Thunderstar Pact to
the goblin to teach Aht the
magic Lightning Star Position.{end}

[00000034]
Give the Firestar Pact to
the goblin to teach Aht the
magic Fire Star Position.{end}

[00000035]
Give the Icestar Pact to the
goblin to teach Aht the
magic Ice Star Position.{end}

[00000036]
Give the Meteorite Pact to the
goblin to teach Aht the
technique Dancing Star.{end}

[00000037]
Bring Bergas the Strongman Book
and defeat him to teach Gafka
a new technique.{end}

[00000038]
Bring Bergas the Tristrike Book
and defeat him to teach Gafka
a new technique.{end}

[00000039]
Bring Bergas the Wind God Book
and defeat him to teach Gafka
a new technique.{end}

[0000003A]
Bring Bergas the Omnipedia and
defeat him to teach Gafka
a new technique.{end}

[0000003B]
Rosch's Gauntlet is incomplete.
If you were to bring Sonja an
Impale Core...{end}

[0000003C]
Rosch's Gauntlet is incomplete.
If you were to bring Sonja a
Blast Core...{end}

[0000003D]
Rosch's Gauntlet is incomplete.
If you were to bring Sonja an
Haste Core...{end}

[000000C7]
This event doesn't occur.{end}
