:00000006:

[00000001]
He was extremely popular with
the people of our nation.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
My father grew afraid...
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
He dismisssed my brother's
idealism as empty words at
first.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
But slowly, he came to realize
that he would be replaced.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
The people would chase him off
of his throne, and my brother
would rule as the true king...
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
And he would be forever judged
a fool by history.{end}
