:00000005:

[00000001]
In order to succeed me, you first
had to awaken the White Chronicle
and gain its power.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
And so I gave you the book before
sending you on an impossible
mission.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
I hoped to show you the world's
true nature, to train you, and
to awaken the White Chronicle.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
What I didn't expect was for that
awakening to happen much sooner
than I planned...
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
Or that you had the acting skill
to hide it from me.{end}
