:00000006:

[00000001]
(All things considered, it makes
the most sense to assume that
Hugo's words are a trap.)
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
(But for a man who should be
completely cornered, he has a
lot of confidence...)
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
(And most convincing of all, he
knows about my ability to travel
through time...)
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
(That being the case, I can't
just write off his words as
the ravings of a lunatic.)
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
(This power of Noah... If I were
to obtain it, I might be able to
stop the desertification...)
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
(Can I take this leap of faith,
knowing the danger? I have to
think about this one carefully.){end}
