:00000004:

[00000001]
Prince Ernst never was very
bright...
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
If only he hadn't been so spoiled
as to defy my late husband, the
throne could have been his.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Then again, that is what made it
possible for me to become queen
after Victor's death...
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
The one respect in which your
brother's actions worked in
Granorg's favor.{end}
