:00000004:

[00000001]
My brother was always one to put
his ideals into practice. He did
many things for the country.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
He dug irrigation ditches, built
bridges, erected bulletin boards,
assisted the tradesmen...
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
The Resistance was originally
formed by those my brother had
become especially close to.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
They grieved over his death and
came together to protect his
ideals.{end}
