:00000004:

[00000001]
Hedge... How many years has it
been since you came to this
land?
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
You still don't understand
the desert culture!
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
First and foremost, we provide
entertainment for our guests,
even if they are our enemies!
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
It may be for entertainment
only, but we still give it 100%!
That is the way of the desert!{end}
