:00000005:

[00000001]
...I don't know about that.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
That bastard didn't even know
how many lives he ruined...
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
He atoned for nothing. He threw
his responsibility away and just
ran off to his precious Noah.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
And then he died with the
happiest smile in the world.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
...In that respect, maybe he's
the winner after all.{end}
