:00000005:

[00000001]
Right. On the one hand you have
the Court Knight Dias, the most
active of the Granorg army...
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
And on the other, the scholar
Selvan, with an iron grip on
their Parliament.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Plus, Palomides the Executioner,
Dias' right-hand man, is supposed
to be there too.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Going to Granorg is putting
yourself amongst the wolves.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
Nobody would do that unless they
were willing to throw their life
away.{end}
