:00000005:

[00000001]
Have you found the others?
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
They are a woman in Celestia,
a man in Granorg, and a boy
in Alistel.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Let me give you the password
once more, just in case:
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
"Time carries away all things.
The past shapes the future.
Hope is in the past."
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
I hear you have a multitude of
tasks, but I hope you do this.{end}
