:00000006:

[00000001]
That's the problem... It's
basically impossible to get...
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
The green I need comes from
shaving down an ore called
Almakalite.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Only one artisan knew the
precise proportions to make
the perfect green.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
But he died in an accident
at Alma Mine...
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
He loved Gran Plain, so
I wanted this painting to
be a tribute to him...
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
And if I don't have that
paint, this just won't be
a fitting tribute.{end}
