:00000009:

[00000001]
Do you understand now?
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
These two ingredients can never
be in their prime at the same
time.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
That is why this dish will never
live up to its true potential.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
In terms of the sauce, I have
nothing bad to say about it.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
I don't know how you found ripe
Cornet vegetables at this time
of year, but they're very rich.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
However, the sauce is doing all
of the work here. The meat
itself is lacking.
{FD14}{end}

[00000007]
It's proof that the boar meat is
not at its finest.
{FD14}{end}

[00000008]
You went into this knowing
nothing of the dish, or the
reason for my obsession...
{FD14}{end}

[00000009]
Come back when you understand!{end}
