:00000004:

[00000001]
And what will you do when the
mass-produced models have a
critical flaw!?
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Theory isn't practice! A weapon
isn't truly usable until there's
data that supports it!
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Mechanical improvements, made
little by little--that's what
will create the perfect weapon!
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
And for that I need data. Raw
data, as much as I can get.{end}
