:00000004:

[00000001]
Indeed I have, Sir Hedge. Look
to the west.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
This man is unmatched in
strength. He has never lost a
battle, in fact.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
The one to the east... I've not
seen his skill, but he was some
kind of knight or mercenary.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
I believe he is the perfect
opponent to bring out the best
from my gladiator.{end}
