:00000006:

[00000001]
Stocke headed to Granorg without
waiting for the arrival of the
Gutrals.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Having gotten as far as the
palace, Stocke believed that all
was going according to plan.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Instead, he walked into Dias'
trap.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
They saw no soldiers in the city
only because the palace was to
be the stage of the ambush.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
The palace gates closed behind
them, and the onslaught of an
entire army surged forth...
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
Stocke and his allies were truly
trapped like rats in a cage...{end}
