:00000006:

[00000001]
Aht gathered her life energy
and used it to burst through
the power of Chi.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
The gladiator's shock gave
Stocke his opening, and he
emerged as the victor.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
But with her life energy sapped,
Aht vanished from the world...
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Stocke continued to win, and
eventually came to be known as
the land's strongest warrior.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
Aht gave her life for his
victory, and Stocke knows he
cannot afford to lose.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
His fight will carry on for as
long as he lives...{end}
