:00000004:

[00000001]
There's always that possibility.
Actually... There's no way they
wouldn't anticipate it.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
But the enemy is focused on the
Sand Fortress right now. They
don't have many troops to spare.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
So we can probably accomplish
this mission with a small
brigade.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
...That's what headquarters
thinks, anyway.{end}
