:00000005:

[00000001]
Thank you. Well, to get straight
to the point, Sonja's been
acting odd for a while now.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
She seems... distracted. Like
her mind is elsewhere, and
that's not like her at all.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
The problem is, I think it's
starting to affect her work.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
The only staff allowed on this
floor are hand-picked from the
best of the best.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
So as her colleague, I'd really
like to see her return to form.
Think you can help?{end}
