:00000005:

[00000001]
I know this guy, okay? He's a
real strange one.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
He never speaks up for himself,
so I never know what's on
his mind.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
And he tends to jump straight
into certain death all on his
own, without letting us know.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
He's tough enough, and he tells
us not to worry...
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
But I can't help myself. I can't
stop worrying anyway.{end}
