:00000006:

[00000001]
...Pardon me. I'll answer your
question now.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
As you said, the power of Flux
is passed down through Granorg's
royal family.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
But it is definitely not the
power to turn people to sand.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
It is used to bring the unstable
Mana of this land back into
its natural balance.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
Using the power of Flux to bring
stability back to this land...
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
This has been the duty of our
royal family for generations.{end}
