:00000005:

[00000001]
Prepare to begin the mission!
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Everyone must stick together at
all times inside the mine.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Whatever happens, under no
circumstances should you go
off alone!
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
We'll leave a detachment here to
guard the entrance.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
If the enemy should happen to
reach this point, they must be
stopped at all costs.{end}
