:00000007:

[00000001]
Stocke's awakening was necessary
for my desired future... The only
question was, how to trigger it?
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
After trying out countless
permutations of history, I
realized he needed comrades.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Partners with some skill, yet not
so valuable that Stocke would
depend too much on them...
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
They would be the key to Stocke's
awakening. That's when I laid
eyes on you two...
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
All I needed to do then was to
get you in my debt and have you
leave your mercenary unit.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
So I animated a monster's corpse
and eliminated the unit, making
it look like an accident.
{FD14}{end}

[00000007]
Though it took some doing to
manipulate it so that only you
two survived...{end}
