:00000006:

[00000001]
Though Skalla has been taken,
it's Cygnus territory from
here on out.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
I won't let you through, even
if it means we have to fight
to the death.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
...What? You want to be let
through because you're headed
to Forgia?
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Well... You do have a
Gutral with you...
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
I guess you're not from the
Alistel army after all.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
You may pass.{end}
