:00000006:

[00000001]
Ah, the "Wind God" Book. This
contains the secret skill
"Wind God Strike".
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
This skill will prove to
assist you in battle.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Now... Do you feel that Gafka
is capable of besting me in
combat?
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
I will gladly duel with him
if he is ready to face me.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
But, Gafka must be willing
to put his life on the line.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
A warrior must risk all to
learn these skills.{end}
