:00000007:

[00000001]
Thank you!
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Let's see... The man I want you
to talk to is named Berman. He
was in Alma Mine not long ago.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
He was a mercenary at Cygnus but
was recruited for his skills,
and now works at Alma Mine.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
He's known as the Legendary
Engineer...
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
But after the mine closed,
nobody knows where he went.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
I wanted to contact him before
the mine closed, but...
{FD14}{end}

[00000007]
If you find him, please ask him
if he would like to work for
Alistel.{end}
