:00000005:

[00000001]
If you're with Princess Eruca,
then you've chosen a side.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
And I'd rather side with you
than Dias.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
We were going to meet with Dias
to discuss the political
obstacles...
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
But he's always looked down on
us as mercenaries, like he's so
high and mighty. I hate him.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
...Although I suppose it's more
than that. I don't like
Granorg's entire regime.{end}
