:00000008:

[00000001]
Ooh, you're a bit too late.
I don't have any more.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
I sold it all to Mr. Kaizan
when he stopped by here.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
It's not like I can make it
again, either.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
I'd have to start by mining
the ore again... And this is
gonna be a battlefield soon!
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
If you need some, go ask
Mr. Kaizan for it.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
He's a traveling artist.
I heard he's going to Alistel
next.
{FD14}{end}

[00000007]
You should go see him there.
{FD14}{end}

[00000008]
But if you wait too long,
he'll head off somewhere
else, so don't waste time.{end}
