:00000004:

[00000001]
Tch... No wonder they're sending
in such low numbers...
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
But we can't just defy our
orders. We still have to go to
the Sand Fortress.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
On top of that, we'll be
fighting alongside Field Marshal
Viola on the front lines.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Wouldn't you agree that at least
that part is in Alistel's best
interests?{end}
