:00000004:

[00000001]
Well, I'd appreciate if you kept
this quiet, but... The Conuts
absorb Mana efficiently.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Alistel's thaumachines are
powered by Mana, and gathering
a lot of it is a tough job.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
If my project is completed, we
can mass produce the thaumachines
and eventually win the war!
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
So it's imperative that we learn
how to cultivate the Conuts!{end}
