:00000006:

[00000001]
Go through the Sand Fortress
anyway.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
The Sand Fortress and Alma Mine
are equally dangerous, mind you.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
But if it's a choice between a
battle that's over and one that's
only going to get fiercer...
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Take the Sand Fortress. They're
not guarding it much, anyway.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
Palomides of the Dias Knights has
already gone home.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
That much you can count on.{end}
