:00000006:

[00000001]
The keys to Gutral combat are
the fist and Chi.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
One who has mastered both, and
truly believes in himself, is
called a Beast God.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
There is a ritual to becoming
a Beast God, but no one has
ever become one.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
And, honestly, I don't know if
having a Beast God's power
will be of any use to you.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
But, if you do seek it... Find
the "Beast God's Nail" that
was taken from our village.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
If you do, bring it back to
Forgia, and we'll try to
perform the ritual.{end}
