:00000005:

[00000001]
When we lost the battle, Dias
took a sword that was a family
treasure from me.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
It has a floral pattern, and
it's the only one of its kind.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
I won't go home without it.
That's why I left the army to
come here.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
I've been watching Dias to find
the right time to reclaim it.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
...Damn it! If only I'd killed
him, then this city wouldn't be
burning down right now...{end}
