:00000005:

[00000001]
Oh, it will work. The enemy's
morale has dropped significantly.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
They lost Skalla, after all...
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
...To a supposedly lowly Rebel
army that's taken the offensive
nevertheless.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Knowing that must be incredibly
galling for them.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
If we press and take out the
commander at the Sand Fortress,
the battle will be quickly won.{end}
