:00000006:

[00000001]
It didn't work. My father
wasn't impressed at all.
I have failed.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Cornet Village vegetables' window for
peak freshness is very brief.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Any vegetables that travel from
Cornet Village to Granorg are past their
prime. All gourmands know this.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
...I still have faith in that
dish. There's gotta be some
way to get it just right...
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
But, honestly, I don't really
know for certain. It's not like
it's ever actually been made.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
I'll start from scratch and try
to create something original
that will wow my father.{end}
