:00000007:

[00000001]
Alistel Castle
Noah Square
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
The savior Noah delivered Alistel
from Granorg's oppression at the
young age of 16.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
He is revered as a saint, but 70
years later, he no longer makes
public appearances.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
When Noah has a proclamation to
deliver, General Hugo serves as
his mouthpiece.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
These proclamations are delivered
in a corner of Alistel Castle
commonly known as Noah Square.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
The common folk are not normally
permitted, but on the eve of his
proclamations, it is opened up.
{FD14}{end}

[00000007]
The people come in throngs, eager
for Noah's reassurance in a time
of war and uncertainty...{end}
