:00000005:

[00000001]
The keys to this coup are the
three major figures of Granorg.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Queen Protea, Count Selvan and
his assembly, and the military
leader Dias.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
If they all need to be dealt
with, then the three of us can
handle it ourselves.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
We won't go looking for fights.
All we'd need is backup to help
get us in the door.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
It'll help keep your casualties
to a minimum, as well.{end}
