:00000005:

[00000001]
The original meaning of the
act of stringing beast nails
into a necklace is admonition.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
To control the power of beasts
with the wisdom and heart of
man... That is Beastkind.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
But be careful. That nail is
not just a reminder.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
It is also key to releasing
your humanity, to become a
true beast. I chose not to.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
Yet, if you have foes you must
defeat, take that path. Master
Galva will open the door.{end}
