:00000005:

[00000001]
Oh, so you are a talented
performer as well? There is truly
more to you than meets the eye.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Yet... You may not need to.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
There aren't any major checkpoints
until we reach Alistel.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
And we may just be able to claim
that you're a bodyguard that we
hired.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
In any case...{end}
