:00000006:

[00000001]
It all happened so quickly.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Rosch killed Marco and Eruca...
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Before losing his life as a
result of the wounds Eruca
inflicted on him.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Now Stocke is pursued by Alistel
soldiers, with nowhere to call
home...
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
He continues to stay on the move
along with Raynie and Aht.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
With Eruca gone, however, the
only means of saving the world
is utterly lost.{end}
