:00000006:

[00000001]
Ah, so you have found the
"Strongman" Book. This has the
secret Musou skill within it.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
If you acquire this skill,
it will make your battles
much easier.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Now, about this duel between
Gafka and myself... Is he
prepared to face me in battle?
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
If he is up to the challenge,
bring him to me, and I'll put
him to the test.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
However, Gafka must be willing
to fight for his life.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
That's how important these
skills are!{end}
