:00000004:

[00000001]
The kingdom of Granorg was
founded by that empire's imperial
priests. We are their bloodline.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
And through that blood, we have
inherited the ability to control
Mana, be it ever so slightly.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Thus, we also inherited a duty.
A duty to keep the Mana of the
entire continent stable.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
It's a spell that we in the
royal family refer to as "the
ritual."{end}
