:00000006:

[00000001]
That's right.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
We should also discuss your
injuries.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
You changed history so that you
never fought Palomides, yet your
wounds did not disappear.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
There is a reason for this.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
There are two types of time.
One the whole world experiences,
and one limited to you.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
Even though you alter the world's
time, your own time will not be
reversed.{end}
