:00000005:

[00000001]
I don't know how these people
could have made the impossible
a reality.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
But I'm sure they did something
extraordinary to get ahold of
these ingredients.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
They're hard to come by to begin
with, being separated by such
long distances...
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
I hoped that one day, the land
would be peaceful enough to
make them traded with ease...
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
That's why we chefs have to
keep refining our skill, so that
maybe one day, that comes true.{end}
