:00000005:

[00000001]
How many Sacrifices so far have
died for that cause!?
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
And how many more will give their
lives in the years to come!?
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Some express regret for their
deaths, but sentiment is cheap.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
And even when the barbaric
practice continues, it only
postpones the inevitable...
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
Yet the caster comes away so
satisfied, as if they've saved
the world!{end}
