:00000005:

[00000001]
Ah! So you understand!
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
You've been a wise one since you
were a boy. You were closer to
me than to your father...
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Your dedication made me happy,
and I often took you out of the
castle...
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
So come with me, Ernst!
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
And we'll live and travel through
this dying world together, just
as we did before.{end}
