:00000008:

[00000001]
It was a long time ago...
Our village wasn't here, and
we didn't have a barrier.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Since we Satyros have the
power to control Mana...
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Hugo took an interest in us
and stormed our lands.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Our homes were almost entirely
destroyed. Those who survived
hid in the forest.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
It was Samra who decided to
do something at this time.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
He went to Alistel alone, to
make sure this incident would
never be repeated.
{FD14}{end}

[00000007]
He wanted to create a world
where everyone could live
together in harmony.
{FD14}{end}

[00000008]
...And that was the last time
I ever saw him.{end}
