:00000004:

[00000001]
Just because it's a legend
doesn't mean it's entirely
untrue. Think about it.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Once Protea took the throne, the
desertification intensified. And
monsters increased as well.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
This is all because Protea isn't
upholding her responsibilities.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
...Wasn't Alistel fighting
Granorg to correct that very
situation?{end}
