:00000005:

[00000001]
It's not that simple. The Core
Parts are the basis for control
of the Gauntlet's movement.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
I didn't realize until I had him
on the table how fierce the
battle must have been...
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
The Core Parts that should've
been in his Gauntlet were broken.
Completely unrecoverable.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
I could make new ones from
scratch, but I'd need a facility
like the one at Alistel Castle.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
Or if I could get my hands on an
unused Gauntlet, I could salvage
Core Parts from that.{end}
