:00000004:

[00000001]
No, we don't. If the power of
Flux in the Royal Hall has been
sealed...
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
The world's Mana can't stabilize,
which could cause catastrophes
even beyond the desertification.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
If that were to happen, things
would be too far gone for the
ritual to right them again.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
We must somehow stop him and
free the power of Flux...!{end}
