:00000005:

[00000001]
Oh, it's you guys. I wish I
could jump out and shout, "Got
you! Ahahah!" or something.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
But you've caught us in a bit
of a rut.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
We're no good at stealing, and
you beat us in a fight. We're
supposed to be aces at this!
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Bro's in the pits about the way
things've turned out lately.
How can I cheer him up a bit?
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
Maybe you guys could help a
feller out? It's a cryin' shame
to see him like this.{end}
