:00000005:

[00000001]
Their alliance was made quite
clear by the coded document that
Stocke stole.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
These people were manipulating
the war from the beginning for
little more than power.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Hugo waited as long as possible
to invade Granorg, and acted just
before anyone grew suspicious.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
That gave Selvan enough time to
minimize the casualties...
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
...And as a result, Queen Protea
was surrendered and executed
just the other day.{end}
