:00000005:

[00000001]
Indeed, using the whole of
Alistel for one man's gain is
not something we can forgive.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Which brings us to Noah and
Hugo. They've moved their base
of operations to Granorg.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
They hope to bring out a full-
scale "enlightenment" to the
people there...
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Everything went according to
plan with Hugo's speech, too.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
It seems they will launch their
offensive against Cygnus and
Celestia to fuel their hatred.{end}
