:00000006:

[00000001]
You do indeed.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Plus, Stocke was a military man
for a year before Heiss formed
Special Intelligence.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
With Specint still an unofficial
outfit, on paper, Stocke is still
a soldier.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
When you think about it that
way, it's only natural for
Stocke to be recalled.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
There's no reason to let Heiss
hog the top talent for his
unofficial pet projects.
{FD14}{end}

[00000006]
Though I suppose it's his pet
project that's saved Alistel
more than once...{end}
