:00000004:

[00000001]
Hugo's thaumachine corps invaded
Celestia and killed countless
Beastkind.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
He was after Celestia's abundance
of Mana... A power source for
thaurmaments, in other words.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Fennel is overseeing the creation
of more powerful thaurmaments
even now.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
You've been on a mission, so you
might not realize it, but the
nation's in shambles.{end}
