:00000004:

[00000001]
Mimel used to be a mercenary.
She was heavily wounded in
battle, and can't fight now.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
When Heiss found me and I had
to move to Alistel, I asked
her to come with me.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
I asked Heiss to pull some
strings, but you can't get a
Specint job if you can't fight.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
That's why she ended up
working in a restaurant in
Alistel.{end}
