:00000004:

[00000001]
You went back and averted the
deaths of Raynie and Marco.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Rosch's death happens further in
the future, but it too can be
averted in the same way.
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
Even should that future come to
pass, you can revisit it and
change history.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
And this is the primary juncture
at which you may do so.{end}
