:00000004:

[00000001]
I saw those walking thaumachines
the homeland sent over.
I don't like 'em.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
Those aren't weapons. A real
weapon is something you grasp
in your hands...
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
If you can't feel the weight
and balance... You can't call
that a weapon. Psh.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Oh, man... Just thinking about
the sound they make cutting
through the air...{end}
