:00000005:

[00000001]
I told you, I might not win.
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
I've got to do what I can.
Maybe the truth spreads,
maybe it doesn't...
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
But I'll be giving it my all,
and that's better than throwing
my life away.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
Oh, please take a copy of our
book.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
You guys seem pretty tough, so
I think you'll be particularly 
interested in its inserts.{end}
