:00000005:

[00000001]
The Dias Knights were fierce
opponents...
{FD14}{end}

[00000002]
But we have won the day!
{FD14}{end}

[00000003]
It's a shame that their leader
escaped, but I wouldn't follow
him too doggedly.
{FD14}{end}

[00000004]
You never know what kind of
ambush he'll have left for us
along his escape route.
{FD14}{end}

[00000005]
No, we should return to the
castle and prepare ourselves
for the next battle.{end}
